MY FAVORITE MOMENT
THAT TODAY WAS
HELPING THOSE KIDS
AT THE CENTER.
I CAN FEEL
THEIR STRUGGLES, BUT
THEY HAVE THE
WORDS IN THEIR
HEAD, BUT THEY
JUST CAN'T SAY
IT. YEAH. DO
YOU REMEMBER WHAT
THAT FELT LIKE?
I FELT LIKE
A BALL STUCK
IN YOUR THROAT.
DOES IT GET
FRUSTRATING? YEAH, IT
DOES GET FRUSTRATING
AFTER A WHILE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE
LUCKY BECAUSE YOU
GOT LANGUAGE, BUT
THERE ARE KIDS
AT YOUR AGE
THAT CAN'T, STILL
CAN'T SPEAK. DO
I HAVE AUTISM
STILL? DO YOU
FEEL LIKE YOU
STILL HAVE AUTISM?
YEAH, SOMETIMES I
DO, BUT SOMETIMES
I DON'T. WHAT
DO YOU MEAN?
WHEN I ACT
A LITTLE CRAZY,
THAT'S SOMETIMES WHEN
I START TO
CRY AND FEEL
SENSITIVE. THAT'S WHEN
I FEEL LIKE
I HAVE AUTISM.
WHAT ABOUT FRIENDSHIP?
YEAH, THAT KIND
OF FEELS LIKE
I HAVE AUTISM
TOO. WHEN I
ACT COOL AROUND
FRIENDS AT THAT
MOMENT, I DON'T
SEEM I REALLY
HAVE IT THEN.
BUT DO YOU
SOMETIMES FEEL LIKE
YOU DON'T HAVE
FRIENDS BECAUSE YOU
HAVE AUTISM? YEAH.
YOU DO? YEAH,
SOMETIMES I SEE
PEOPLE WHO LIKE
ME SOMETIMES BECAUSE
I HAVE AUTISM.
RIGHT. WHEN YOU
WERE LITTLE, YOU
WERE REALLY HAVING
A HARD TIME
CONNECTING AND MAKING
FRIENDS. THEY DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND WHO YOU
WERE.
RIGHT? YEAH. WHAT
DID THEY ASK
YOU TO SAY?
I ASKED YOU
IN THE BOOTY
HOLE. ARE YOU
KIDDING ME? YOU
HAD BOYS THAT
WERE SENDING YOU
UP TO GIRLS
SAYING DISGUSTING THINGS.
THEY MADE ME
GO IN THE
GIRLS' BATHROOM. I
DID TO MAKE
FRIENDS. I DIDN'T.
ANYTIME YOU HAVE
SOMEONE THAT DOESN'T
REALLY UNDERSTAND YOU,
THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO REALLY KNOW
HOW TO LOVE
YOU BECAUSE THEY
DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU ARE. I
DON'T WANT YOU
TO FEEL SAD
ABOUT NOT HAVING
25, 30 FRIENDS
BECAUSE YOU ONLY
REALLY NEED ONE
OR TWO GOOD
FRIENDS, RIGHT? YEAH.
MOM HAS ANTI
-TERRY. I HAVE
WONDER. YOU HAVE
WONDER. YOU ALWAYS
LOOK OUT FOR
ME. YOU WOULD
WONDER EVER PUT
YOU IN A
BAD POSITION WHERE
YOU WERE EITHER
IN HARM'S WAY
OR YOU DID
SOMETHING INAPPROPRIATE. HE
WOULD NEVER DO
THAT. NO. THAT'S
A REAL FRIEND.
THAT IS HOW
YOU JUDGE WHO
IS YOUR FRIEND,
WHO HAS YOUR
BACK, WHO'S LOOKING
OUT FOR YOU.